tattoo.com 2019-12-09

# Privacy Policy - Tattoo.com

Tattoo.com.com is committed to protecting your privacy in a manner that will allow you to use our services with confidence and comfort. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to describe:

  1. What information Tattoo.com collects
  2. How we use it
  3. Your control over the information you give us
  4. How we protect your information from theft or unauthorized use

This Privacy Policy is subject to change from time to time, so please check back each time you access this site. Use of the services offered at this site constitutes acceptance of the terms of this Policy. If you have a question about the Privacy Policy, please contact our customer service department.

 **The Information We Collect**

Any information that you provide through the Tattoo.com registration process or responses to offers made available to you is completely voluntary. You always have a choice whether or not to disclose information requested in the survey, registration or offer. The information we collect includes contact and postal information (such as name, mailing address and telephone number), e-mail address and demographics information (such as age, interests and additional information). Your participation in these questions is completely voluntary.

We cannot accept information from those under the age of 18 years. Those under 18 cannot participate in contest and promotions offered by Tattoo.com or the promotion sponsor. In addition, we do not knowingly collect, use or disseminate any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 18. If, however, we become aware that personally identifiable information regarding a child under the age of 18 has been collected, we will delete it from our records. We encourage parents and guardians to participate in and supervise the online activities of their children.

 **How We Use It**

Your information will be used to improve and personalize the offers Tattoo.com sends to you and all of our members, to provide marketing offers to you, and to contact you with regards to your entry into our contest promotion. By providing your e-mail address to Tattoo.com, you are agreeing to receive e-mail messages from Tattoo.com and/or third party marketers. Tattoo.com and third party marketers may send you e-mail messages regarding marketing offers from other reputable organizations whose products and services we think you might find interesting. Contact, postal, e-mail address and demographic information may be shared with third party marketers for such marketing purposes. In addition, Tattoo.com provides services for direct marketing applications including lookup and reference, data enhancement, suppression and validation.

 **The Controls You Have on the Information You Share**

If you do not want us to share contact, postal, e-mail address and demographic information with third party marketers, we can add your name to our “do-not-share” or “do-not-call” list. Please visit [http://www.tattoo.com/contact](https://www.tattoo.com/contact) to request to be added to this list. Additionally, you may request to unsubscribe from all Tattoo.com related emails by clicking the unsubscribe button at the bottom of the email.  To remove yourself from third party mailing lists, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided or contact the third party directly with your request for removal.

 **Security**

Tattoo.com takes every precaution to protect your information. When you submit information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. We take very seriously our responsibility to protect your private information. Internally, we restrict access to your information to employees who need access to the information in order for them to do their jobs. These employees are limited in number and are committed to our privacy and security policies. Finally, the servers on which we store your information are kept in a secure environment.

 **Additional Information**  
**Cookies and Pixel Tags**

We use persistent, non-identifying cookies if, and only if, you request that we remember your entry or registration information. If we remember your information, you can avoid re-typing that information the next time you enter a survey or contest. You can still use our site even if you have turned off your browser’s ability to receive cookies. Cookies also enable us to better match your interests with marketing offers from reputable companies. Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site and in HTML e-mail messages (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. Our e-mail messages may contain pixel tags for the purpose of determining if your e-mail software or service can display html-formatted e-mail and whether our members open such email messages. Additionally, third party pixel tags may be displayed on our site or in our e-mail messages.

 **Log Files**

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track visitor traffic, and aggregate demographic data. We may link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information to document your registration IP address, date and time, detect and investigate malicious activity, as necessary, comply with our corporate policies, including but not limited to legal obligations, dispute resolution and enforcement of our agreements and to assist us with enhancing and personalizing content and your online experience.

 **Third Party Ads**

Tattoo.com works with third parties to serve ads and promotions through this site as well as to assist us in managing customer information and to communicate with you. These parties include, but are not limited to Google, Revcontent, and DoubleClick DART. To find out more about how these third parties manage the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please visit the privacy policy on their web sites.

 **Third Party Services**

From time-to-time, we may partner with other parties to provide specific services. It may be necessary to share names, or other contact information with third parties to provide these services.

 **Links**

This website may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we, Tattoo.com, are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by our website. When you are on the Tattoo.com site or are accessing a Tattoo.com promotion through an advertising vehicle, and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with Tattoo.com. Promotions, surveys and other contest offerings may be sponsored, or co-sponsored, by another company. Some or all of the data collected during such a program may be shared with the marketing partner. But remember, your participation is always voluntary.

 **Sale, Merger or Reorganization**

Tattoo.com may transfer, sell or assign information concerning your use of this Site, including without limitation, personally identifiable information that you provide and other information concerning your use of the Site as a result of a sale, merger, consolidation, changing control, transfer of substantial assets, reorganization or liquidation of Tattoo.com.

 **Special Disclosure Exceptions**

In some cases, we may disclose your personal information with other third parties if we are required to do so by law or we in good faith believe that such action is necessary to: Comply with the law; Protect and defend our rights and property; Protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the Site and/or Tattoo.com; or Protect the personal safety or property of our users or the public.

 **Special Rights for Residents of Certain States**

If you are a California resident or another state with specific laws relating to the collection and use of information, you may have specific rights not set forth in this policy. For example, California residents have the right to receive: a) information identifying any third party company(ies) to whom we may have disclosed, within the past calendar year, personal information pertaining to you and your family for the company’s direct marketing purposes; and b) a description of the categories of personal information disclosed. To obtain such information you must make a request in writing. Your request must include your registration email address, the site name you visited and a return address on a prepaid mailing envelope, or it will not be processed. We will not honor such requests more than once per calendar year. Requests made via email will not be accepted.

Please mail your request to Customer Service Manager, 1461 Lawrence Dr. 2nd Floor Thousand Oaks, CA 91320

 **Notification of Changes**

Tattoo.com may from time to time, amend this Policy, in whole or in part, at its sole discretion. Please check this page each time you access this site for changes. Use of this site shall constitute acceptance of the change and this Policy.
